Hey guys, it's Syd.
I have been avoiding filming this video because I don't want to know how much I spent in New York.
And I also don't want you guys to know how much I spent in New York.
Every time I leave my apartment, minimum $100 down the drain.
And I don't know how.
That is what inspired this video is I looked at my credit card and I was like, what happened?
So yeah, I'm getting my day started late.
It's 1 p.m. But I thought I would pick up my camera, film how much I spend every single day in a week living in New York.
Please go easy on me, guys.
Starting the day out strong, just spent $9 on a latte.
Something about me that I'm not proud of is I will spend all of my money on coffee.
Here's how I justify this.
Because I work for myself, I work from home, and I don't have an office space.
I like to go out to a coffee shop every single morning because it gets me out, it gets me in like a routine.
So I consider this $9 latte basically my rent to work at the coffee shop for about 3-4 hours.
This is how I can justify this in my head.
This is how it makes sense to me.
Even though $9 is actually absurd, I do have a punch cart here.
I'm a loyal member.
Every eight coffees, I get a free one.
Everything adds up.
So I'm going to work here and enjoy this $9 latte.
When I got home, I desperately needed to do laundry.
One thing about my apartment is I don't have any unit laundry, which means I do have to pay for it.
It's $3 to wash.
So threw my laundry in.
While my laundry's going, I thought I'd go for a little walk.
I love walking on the West Side Highway.
It's so beautiful.
This is my like gym replacement in the summertime often and it's also free, so that's a perk.
So I just texted one of my friends and she's gonna meet me down there in 20 minutes.
That's my update.
It is a little bit chilly.
I'm having one of those weeks where I just I've been feeling so lonely I feel like I miss my family like extra oh hold on hello Melissa
I think you have the wrong number I'm with Helga hi everyone guys Helga's like a real life angel she's just like the sweetest person ever my mood's
lifted I'm no longer lonely I show them your nails oh yes of course look at her nails these are real right they're real yeah yeah yeah
real nails real look how beautiful oh my nails could never do your
nails All right guys, I'm back for laundry.
That means I'm about to spend three more dollars.
Dinner is served.
This, oh wait.
We do care if you're in the background.
Like, hey, Amar.
She's cooking dinner.
I'm about to sit down to eat dinner.
We actually usually eat together.
We usually like coordinate our meals, but I was just in a rush.
I'm having leftovers.
This is one of our favorite meals to have.
It's just so easy and it's actually makes for good leftovers.
This is one of my rotation dinners though.
It's ground beef, white sweet potato, cottage cheese.
Okay, hear me out.
It's good.
I don't know why.
I really doubted this, but together it tastes great.
Iceberg lettuce and hot honey This is kind of like a little bowl that Olivia came up with and showed I been trying to not eat out so
much during the week One because financially Two just it like so much better healthier And I think I've been doing a lot better at that this year.
You guys know I've been golfing and I really don't have any golf clothes.
Not that I need like this perfect outfit, but for like the club, I need something to wear.
I've literally been just wearing leggings.
So I just went on ThredUp and I found a couple things.
I don't know.
I just got this skirt and like tank top.
I love ThredUp.
It's so great.
They have good pieces that are inexpensive.
My total, $55.03.
Not too bad.
These are the things that I got.
I think I'm safe for the night though.
I think I'm done spending money today.
I don't think I'll buy anything else.
I better not.
Good morning.
I was supposed to go to the gym.
Didn't happen.
I actually, I'm kind of upset.
I like set with myself about it.
I'm starting my morning making a Smoothie.
This is my favorite smoothie ever.
I actually got DMs from you guys saying that you made this.
Can't even explain how happy that made me to see you guys making something that I make every day.
I don't know.
It was just so cool.
So many of you guys love it.
It's just the best smoothie recipe ever.
I feel like I really perfected it.
I'm getting coffee with actually a girl who does YouTube too.
Her name's Isa.
If any of you guys watch her or know her, I don't really meet a lot of other creators that often.
Like, I feel like most people socialize more than me.
I think I'm just anti-social or something, but I'm really excited to meet her in person.
This is the secret ingredient in my smoothies, the cacao nibs.
Hey guys, I'm with Isa.
Hi.
We have the same camera look.
Well, you guys can't see mine.
This is the best camera.
Canon, the best.
Face-to-face is what I expected.
Wait, I'm spending, I'm doing what I spend in a day.
Today?
Yes, yes.
Wait.
That's so fun.
That's crazy.
I spent zero dollars because Isa bought me my coffee, guys.
How sweet.
I spent.
Yeah, so Isa spent.
It's too nice.
Wait, she bought some pastries, guys.
You guys have to try Radio Bakery if you're in New York.
Earl Grey Morning Bun and a PB&J croissant.
We're going to do a taste test.
Yes, I have no original idea.
Cheers.
Yeah.
Isn't it good?
So fresh.
They bake it every morning.
What do you rate it?
I give it a nine.
Oh, yeah, that's good.
So I stumbled upon this market.
One of the things I love the most about New York is there's just the most random pop-ups and markets and foods to try.
It looks like they have some Jamaican food.
Kind of like a lot of random things.
And honestly, I'm like a little bit hungry, and I kind of want to try something.
Just something small.
I feel like I need to.
This is so cool, guys.
Like, what is happening?
I just spent $12 on these Brazilian cheese balls.
It comes with this little chive sauce.
I feel like a food reviewer.
Mmm.
This is really good.
It's like a little bit doughy, which I love.
When my parents visit me in a couple weeks, I'm going to take them here.
Worth every penny.
And then this is me running really late later to meet my friend.
I'll go for dinner.
I was at home and suddenly fell asleep for two hours.
I literally never nap, so I don't know what the heck happened.
Anyways, I am going to dinner with my same friend as last night, Helga.
I, it was kind of last minute.
I was just like, wait, what are you doing?
So yeah, we're gonna get Kurobita.
I literally love this spot.
It's so good.
Dinner time.
She's back.
Two days in a row.
I got a summer chicken bowl with pepper, avocado, pineapple.
Helga got salmon ball.
We're so far away from each other.
This is a $20 dinner.
It's gonna be so worth it.
I love this place.
This is a crazy Friday night for us.
What a crazy Friday night, guys.
25-year-old girl in New York.
I'm at Frozen Yogurt by myself.
After dinner, I was walking home.
So I didn't spend any money, actually, on my transportation home.
I like walking in the city when it's warm.
Like, it's just so nice out.
I was walking and I was like, ugh, I want a sweet treat.
And I've been, like, craving frozen yogurt so much the past week.
So I decided to go in, take myself on like a little yogurt date.
I got mini M&Ms and strawberries.
Kind of a vibe in here.
I'm kind of loving this for myself.
I actually did have plans with a friend after this that sort of fell through, which is also why I needed a pick-me-up.
Oh wait, how much was this?
I think it was like eight dollars, guys.
I spent so much of my money on food.
The last time I looked at my Amex bills, all of my money was on food.
You'll see that this week.
Long time no talk.
I'm on my way to dinner.
Today I was stuck in front of my laptop all day long.
Since it's Saturday, my boyfriend and I are going to go on a little dinner date.
One of our favorite restaurants.
It's called One White Street in Tribeca.
So I'm on my way there.
This is my date night outfit.
I'm taking the Cab because I'm running late.
I think it's like $15 ish.
$15 was all I spent on date night because my sweet lovely boyfriend got me dinner.
We had such a great date night and then the next day you are seeing that right.
I am wearing the exact same outfit.
Please don't ask.
We were running a little late.
This was actually Mother's Day so we took an Uber out to see his family.
The only thing I bought this day were flowers for his mom of course.
These ones were beautiful and they were also $60.
Sorry, I'm trying to balance vlogging with my boyfriend versus just being alone.
I usually just try to be in the moment.
Anyways, now you're all caught up.
Good morning guys.
I'm back at the office.
Starting my day as usual, doing work.
I was able to redeem my punch card so I got a free coffee today.
Best possible way to start my day.
So I did spend nothing so far.
Yes, I did forget to show it again before I drank it.
I do have a birthday brunch for my friend in a little bit so I'm gonna go pick up part of her gift for her.
So right across from the coffee shop there's this little gift shop and I need a bag for her birthday gift.
I have like the gift itself.
They have so many cute bags here.
I picked up this very Helga birthday bag.
Also she loves matcha and I saw this matcha chocolate that I had to add to the gift and she also loves flowers and always always gets me
flowers for no reason so I had to also add some and then we surprised her.
It was a surprise birthday brunch and she was actually surprised.
She's usually not.
Brunch ended up being $54 expensive but I've been wanting to
try this place for so long their bagels were really good I'm a sucker for a good bagel then I took an impromptu stop at Walgreens I went
in for one thing I always end up with like five really needed some allergy medication so yes it's true the rumors are true I'm going to the
gym today ever since I got back for my friend's birthday brunch, I was on a two hour and 30 minute hold related to health insurance.
So I think the number one thing I want to do is literally run my anger out on a treadmill.
Try to do the iced protein latte with sugar vanilla.
Good morning guys.
I started the day off with the Dunkin' Latte.
I actually got something different.
I wanted to try their vanilla protein latte and it's really good.
It's really good.
It's like less sweet than I thought, which I kind of like.
$7, but well worth it.
I love Dunkin'.
I'm starting out the day grabbing groceries because I have nothing.
I usually go to Whole Foods just because it's really close to me and I can easily walk there.
Walking home is another story, especially if I have a lot of groceries, so I guess we'll see.
Work out of the day complete because I did just walk home with all my groceries.
I actually really need one of those grocery carts.
Everyone like keeps sending me them.
I did need to stock up on some things and this will be good for me so I don't eat out.
I feel really guilty when I eat out when I have a ton of groceries so I wanted to do a little quick haul.
I love, you guys know I love grocery hauls and I might as well show you my favorite things that I got.
So actually do you guys like grocery hauls, like please let me know.
If it's just me, I'll stop doing them.
Granola, blueberries, and strawberries for yogurt bowls.
Mini bell peppers are the best snack.
Crackers and hummus to go along with it.
Protein powder for my smoothies.
Cacao nibs also for my smoothies.
Bananas.
Frozen kids meals because I'm a child.
I'm addicted to smart sweets.
Frozen yogurt bars.
Ground beef.
Some oatmeals.
And cotton rounds.
That is everything I got.
You know, was it worth $150?
I don't know, but probably not.
Anyways, time to put all of this away in my fridge.
Later that night, my cousin asked me to go see a movie at an outdoor theater in Manhattan.
Update, we're at the movie.
No one's here.
Well, no one's here.
Do you want to say hi?
Hey, what up?
This is my cousin.
I'm Tori, her cousin.
We go way back.
Back.
Birth.
This outdoor theater experience costs $27.
With popcorn, we got the upgrade.
It was 23 if we didn't.
Very worth it.
Well, actually, I don't know yet.
We haven't seen the movie, but.
But this is a fun activity to do that isn't like crazy expensive.
All right, guys.
So we officially made it a week.
Well, six days.
The inevitable time has come.
It is time to see how much I spent.
I'm blurring my feet.
You don't get any ideas.
Do I just rip the band-aid off?
I ended up spending $533.09.
The sad part is this doesn't even include my rent.
Um, I'm trying to look at what I spent the most on, and I feel like a lot of it was food.
Food, coffee, and sweet treats.
Also convenience like Ubering.
To be honest, this was a good week for me.
I didn't make any like insane big purchases.
It can get worse than this.
Having lived in Minnesota before this, New York is so expensive.
People are not lying when they say that.
It is.
You cannot leave the apartment without spending at least 50 bucks.
I feel so lucky to ever even be able to live in New York in the first place, because I never would have been able to afford this
when I was living in Minnesota.
This was fun.
I hope you guys enjoyed this.
Time to sit with this number in my head.
Thanks for watching.
Please don't judge me.
Actually, you can judge me.
It's okay.
See you soon.
Bye.